https://www.tranquilmoney.com/privacy-policy/

About Us
Leadership TeamExperienced professionals lead Tranquilmoney
InvestorsWho are Tranquilmoney investors?
AwardsRecognition for our Healthcare Receivables technology
CollaborationWith Medical Billing and Healthcare Insurance companies
Total Quality ManagementA quality philosophy at Tranquilmoney.
Company TimelineTranquilmoney in the News
MethodologyQuality, reliability and security in Healthcare Receivables management
Physicians
PracticeTracker™ SoftwarePhysicians’ Practice Management software with Billing, EHR & ePrescription
Plans and Pricing
teleClinic™ PlatformSecure video consultation software. Lite edition Free for unlimited use.
Plans and Pricing
PracticeTracker™ ServicesRCM, increase collections and reduce overheads
Pharmacies
PharmTracker™ ServicesReceivables services for retail Pharmacy chains or independent Pharmacies
PharmTracker™ AR FinanceFinancing for independent Pharmacies against Insurance receivables
PharmTracker™ SoftwareAI backed software for managing Pharmacy receivables & reconciliation
AR Finance
Physician AR FinanceFinancing for Physicians against Accounts Receivables
Pharmacy AR FinanceFinancing for independent Pharmacies against Insurance receivables
GENERAL
Tranquilmoney respects the privacy of every individual who visits www.tranquilmoney.com (the "Website"). Tranquilmoney wants you to fully understand what information we gather about you, how that information is collected, and how that information is used and how you can control the collection and/or use of information about you. So, please read this Policy carefully.
PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
There are cases where Tranquilmoney may ask you for personally-identifiable information such as your name, mailing address and email address. We may also collect information from email, letters or other correspondence that you send us. Tranquilmoney will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily, with the exception of your computer's IP address. The IP address is an identifier unique to each computer or internet usage session.
WHEN YOU DO PROVIDE US WITH PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, TRANQUILMONEY MAY
Store and process that information to enhance your experience with Tranquilmoney so that we provide a service that is relevant and easy to use
Use that information to contact you for informational, marketing and promotional purposes on behalf of Tranquilmoney and third parties, including such as welcoming you back to the Web Site or informing you of service enhancements or promotional items
Disclose that information to third parties when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Tranquilmoney's rights or property, other users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities; and
Disclose that information to third parties when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required by law or a court of competent jurisdiction
In addition, as Tranquilmoney continues to develop its business, we may sell or buy other businesses or assets. A buyer or successor will have access to our customer lists as this information is considered a transferable business asset.
Except as stated in this Policy, or as otherwise stated at the time personally-identifiable information is gathered, we will not provide personally-identifiable information to third parties.
NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
Tranquilmoney may also collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information may include your age, gender, interests and preferences and the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to the Web Site. Tranquilmoney may share this information with advertisers, business partners, sponsors or other third parties. For example, Tranquilmoney may inform a sponsor that the users of the Web Site is x percent females and y percent males. This data is used to customize the Web Site's content and advertising, and to deliver a better experience to our users.
CHILDREN
The Web Site is not directed to individuals under thirteen years of age, and Tranquilmoney does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals.
COOKIES
"Cookies" are electronic files on your hard drive. Cookies cannot read data off your hard drive: they store identification information about you. Tranquilmoney, like the operators of many other web sites, uses the cookies to identify you when you visit the Web Site. Tranquilmoney may also use the cookie to recognize you to help ensure the security of confidential information. Tranquilmoney uses the information from cookies to personalize services and determine the amount and type of traffic at the Web Site. Cookies also provide us with information about your "clickstream", that is, the way that you navigate through the Web Site, so that we can better design the Web Site for your use.
Most browsers allow you to disable or delete your cookies. Tranquilmoney would prefer to provide you with personalized services through cookies and not all services may be available to those who disable or delete cookies.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES
The Web Site may provide links to various other web sites. Tranquilmoney assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites you are able to access through the Web Site. These links to other sites do not imply any affiliation or endorsement of a linked site.
SECURITY
The importance of security of all personally-identifiable information associated with our users is of utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. While we strive to protect your personally-identifiable information, Tranquilmoney can not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our on-line products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your personally-identifiable information, we will take reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS
By using the Web Site, you signify your assent to the Tranquilmoney Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Web Site.
MODIFICATION OF THESE TERMS
The process of maintaining this Web Site is an evolving one, and Tranquilmoney may decide at some point in the future to modify these terms. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to the terms will mean you accept those changes.
WHO TO CONTACT
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact Tranquilmoney by telephone at: 212-494-0383; or by email to info@tranquilmoney.com
Download
Submit
Close
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
